Hi ladies hope you're all doing good. So we took a look back at the domination call
and we decided there was something quite important that was missing so we're gonna
chat about it today, and what that is, is really to build a connection and
a relationship with your sub. I think the Dom course is good for giving you
practical things to do with the sub in each aspect of domination. But one thing that
we haven't really touched on is actually building a connection as well. So then you
can take it down any of the aspects and any of the routes that we've taught you on
the course. So the relationship is partly about the Dom Developing her dark feminine
and developing her desire to ask the masculine to perform tasks for her and to be
submissive to her. I recently had a coaching session with mistress Ivy and she taught
me a really amazing template that we can use when interacting with our subs so I
will teach it to you today. Thank you Mistress Ivy for educating us with your knowledge.
And if you haven't done already girls, go and check out the Zoom call that we had
with Mistress Ivy, it's really amazing and there's a lot of useful information in
there, especially if you want to delve into the world of domination. So it's on the
training videos on our website. There are two main prongs when it comes to
the Dom Sub relationship, the first is the sub’s development of himself with self-care
and the second is the sub’s development to become more of a better sub and
more submissive for his mistress. And this can be broken down into four main categories.
The first category is your sub’s development with self-care. The second category
is having your sub perform service tasks for his mistress. The third category is having
your sub perform sexual tasks. And the fourth category is you having your sub perform
devotion tasks. So with that being said the Dom sessions aren't just
like about you telling them what to do, making them do things for you and just you
know, not thinking about them on the other side. Respecting them, you know, it's
about respect, and this is another human on you’re on this journey together. And you're
helping them grow as well, yet they're saving you but you're also helping them
to grow and you're guiding them on this journey. This is basically a huge part of
the Dom Sub relationship. So there are certain things that you can do to develop this
relationship even more. So the first thing we want to look at is his development with
self-care. So you can ask him in your sessions is it any part of your life that you
would like to improve or anything that you need to work on, and you know he may reply
with I should go to the gym more and then you can tell them you've set them now to
go every single day this week, or you know whatever it is. So you can set them tasks
to perform and they can check back in with you on cam the next week that they perform
these tasks or they can email you or text you if you have the tech service on your
profile. So yes, the first one is development with self-care. Secondly, we can look
at his development as a sub and to be you know of service to you. So for example,
you can ask your sub, I want you to go online and find an outfit for me that you think
would look good on me as your mistress. You could ask your sub to go and research
a certain type of book. Because you're into this kind of book and go and find the
best one. You can have him do you know tasks for you and he can report back to you.
Next you could have him do sexual sub task tasks.
So for example, this could be not masturbating until you speak to
him, again not letting him come and having him buy a chastity belt and you know using
it on cam, having him buy nipple clamps and using them on cam, anal training them
as well. You can do stuff like this. So yeah, that's a few suggestions for that one
for a sexual sub act, and finally, you can have your sub
show you acts of devotion. So for example, you could have him come to you every single
week at this certain time or every single day if it got to that point. You can have
him show you devotion in many different ways, you can have him show his devotion by
having them sing you a song, or write you a poem or something like that. So these are
all things that keep your clients engaged when they're outside of cam as well because
that's gonna keep them coming back. So you have that moment with them on camera you're
in control in that moment. But then it's good to have things outside of cam, so
he's always thinking of you doing these things because you've told him to and it
will keep the relationship going and it'll build it stronger. And he will keep
coming back and it'll be a really good money maker for you because these are the
type of clients that you want. So with that being said if you stick to the four categories
when interacting with your sub, you can't really go wrong as you're still in control
of the relationship. You're still in control of where the conversation’s going and
he's still performing for you and showing you his devotion while you're nurturing
him and leading him down a path to become a better person. So finally, let's go over
what we've learned today. So there are two main prongs when it comes to the Dom
Sub relationship. The first prong being the sub’s self development with self-care. And
the second is the sub’s development to become a better sub for his mistress, which
are covered in the four main subcategories that are 1.
Having your sub perform self-care and self-development tasks 2.
Having your sub perform service tasks for his mistress 3.
Having your sub perform sexual tasks and 4.
Having your sub perform devotion tasks. But most importantly what I'd really like
you to take away from this video is just learning to connect with your sub and
find out what he wants what makes him tick, what his desires are, what his fantasies
are and how you're going to deliver this to him, So yeah, I think that's something
to consider about domination. It's not just about being so shut off and just you
know, barking orders. You also need to get to know your sub and understand him and
build a relationship with him Thanks for watching ladies.
I hope that you learned something, and yeah, just let me know if you put it into practice
or if you've got any other suggestions you know of, ideas and stuff like that would
be good to hear from you. But yeah, let me know how you get on and speak soon.